Oh, here's little Ben falling asleep.
벤이 졸고 있는 사진이야
이건 그 뒤에 찍은 거고
A little bit later. Is he gonna sleep?
잠이 와?
잠이 와 죽겠어?
Is he gonna sleep? Is he gonna?
잠이 와?
Yep, out like a light!
내 사진도 있네
- 볼래?
- 아기 똥 치우는 사진이야?
This sure trumps
the "Has he pooped?" series.
우리도 애가 귀여워
Ross, we love him, okay?
But right now he's just
a little fat guy.
하지만 홀딱 벗은 뚱보
아기일 뿐이야
How excited can we get?
사진보는 거 재미없어
안녕
- 어서 와
- 안녕
-What you got?
-400 pictures of Ben on a rug.
뭐야?
벤이 졸고 있는 사진 4백장
- 어디 좀 보자
- 나도 볼래
-Oh, my God!
-Let me see!
The One Where Rachel Finds Out
Here's little Ben nodding off.
벤이 졸고 있는 사진이야
모니카 고모의 귀염둥이
조카 좀 봐
Look at Aunt Monica's little boy!
- 로스 머리를 잡아뜯네
- 어디 좀 봐
-Look, he's got Ross haircut.
-Let me see.
Oh, God!
Is he just the sweetest thing?
너무 귀엽지 않니?
맨날 뽀뽀만 해주고
싶을 것 같아
You must just wanna kiss him all over.
That would be nice.
그러고 싶지
왜?
-Pardon?
-Nothing.
아냐
입 안에 공기가 너무 차서
Just a little extra air in my mouth.
챈들러, 나 좀 도와줘라
나중에 갚을게
Chan, can you help me out?
I'll pay you back.
그래
Right. Including the waffles
last week, you now owe me...
지난주에 꿔간 와플까지
다 해서 17억 달러 빚졌어
... 1 7 jillion dollars.
이번엔 틀림없이 갚을 수 있어
-Really, I'll pay you back this time.
-Where's this money coming from?
돈이 어디서 나서?
뉴욕 의대에서 연구를 하는데
그걸 돕기로 했거든
I'm helping out at the NYU
Med School with research.
무슨 연구?
What kind of research?
그냥 과학적인 거야
Just, you know, science.
과학이라...
Science.
어디서 들어본 것 같은데
Yeah, I think I've heard of that.
수정에 관한 연구야
It's a fertility study.
조이!
Joey, please tell me you're only
donating your time.
가서 시간만 죽이다 온다는
얘긴 아니겠지
Actually, a little more than that.
그런 건 아냐
신이시여, 감사합니다
조이의 분신들을 만드시다니...
Thank you, God.
This will bring us so much joy.
신경쓸 거 없어
별 일 아냐
Come on, it's not that big a deal.
이틀에 한번씩 가서
기부만 해주면 되는 거야
I just go down there
every other day...
...and make my contribution
to the project.
그럼 2주 후에 7백 달러가
들어오는 거라구
But at the end of two weeks,
I get $700!
그 돈 벌려면
손 꽤나 아프겠다
You're gonna be making money
hand over fist.
그래, 실컷 비웃어라
That's funny. Very funny.
난 기분 좋은데
This is great. I actually know
somebody who loves what they do.
자기 일을 좋아하는 사람을
보게 됐잖아
거사를 못 치르면 안되니
너무 무리하지는 마라
But what do you do to unwind
after a tough day at work?
콜슬로우, 건포도는 됐고...
Okay, we got the coleslaw and buns.
귀여운 소랑 칠면조 고기도
준비됐어
The ground-up flesh
of formerly cute cows and turkeys.
너랑 바비큐 파티하니까
너무 좋다
I just love barbecuing with you.
남자들이 왔다!
Men are here!
우리가 불을 피운다
We make fire.
고기를 구워라
Cook meat.
다 끝나면 불은 오줌으로 끈다
Put out fire by peeing,
no get invited back.
귀여운데
조이, 멜라니가 좀 늦겠대
Cute.
-Melanie called. She'll be late.
-Okay.
알았어
두 사람 잘 돼가?
특별한 사이가 된 거야?
How are things going? Is she
becoming your "special someone"?
모르겠어
정말 괜찮은 여자야
I don't know. She's pretty great.
멜라니도 네 과학 프로젝트에
대해 알고 있니?
What does she think of
your little science project?
좋아하는 여자한테 정액 빼느라
바쁘다고 말하라고?
You think I'd tell a girl I like
that I'm also seeing a cup?
그럴 순 없지
Man's got a point.
제일 힘든 건 멜라니가 나랑
관계를 하고 싶어한다는 거야
The tough thing is,
she really wants to have sex.
밝히기는!
Crazy bitch.
아직 일주일이 남았는데
규정을 지켜야 돼
I got a week left to go.
According to the rules...
연구 기간 동안 인간 관계를
가지면 안돼, 무슨 말인지 알아?
... I can't conduct personal
experiments, if you know what I mean.
네 말은 항상 알아들어
Joey, we always know what you mean.
- 안녕
바비큐 파티를 얼마나 오래
하려고?
How long did you think
this barbecue would last?
나 중국 가
-I'm going to China.
-Jeez, you say one thing, and....
말 돌리는 데 선수라니까
중국에 간다고?
-China?
-For the museum. Someone found a bone.
박물관 일이야
누가 뼈를 발견했나봐
우린 뼈가 필요한데
그 사람들은 그걸 싫어해
They don't want us to have it.
그래서 내가 가서
뼈를 달라고 부탁해야 돼
I'm going to try to persuade them.
It's a whole big bone thing.
어쨌든 다 뼈 때문이야
일주일 정도 가 있을 거야
Anyway, I'll be gone for a week.
연락하고 싶어도 안 될 거야
내 여행 일정이야
If you want to reach me, you can't.
So here's my itinerary.
- 이건 내 사진
- 좀 보자
-Here's a picture of me.
-Oh, let me see.
캐롤 집에 갈 때마다
나 잊지 않게 벤한테 보여줘
Could you show it to Ben every now
and then so he doesn't forget me?
알았어
안녕, 벤
네 아빠야
"Hi, Ben. I'm your father."
나는 머리다
"I am The Head!"
바비큐 파티 정말 재밌다
This barbecue's gonna be very fun.
레이첼 있어?
생일 축하 인사나 하고 가려고
I wanted to wish Rachel
a happy birthday before I left.
아니, 칼이랑 나갔어
-She's out having drinks with Carl.
-Hey, who's Carl?
칼이 누구야?
- 커피숍에서 만난 사람 있잖아
- 몰라
That guy she met at the coffeehouse.
- 왜 있잖아, 그때...
- 커피숍에서? 알아
-There's this guy she met at
-The coffeehouse? Right.
봐, 너도 알잖아
So you do know who he is.
I'll go say goodbye to the guys.
애들한테 인사해야겠다
쟤들도 뼈 얘기 좋아할 거야
Hey, you know what?
Tell them that bone story.
안녕
- 어서와
- 안녕
- 나 중국에 가
- 진짜 중국?
-I have to go to China.
-The country?
아니, 엄마 집 찬장에 있는
접시 보러 간다
No, this big pile of dishes
in my mom's breakfront.
칼이 누군지 알아?
Do you know who Carl is?
어디 보자... 알빈, 사이몬,
디오도르... 모르겠는데
Let's see. Alvin, Simon, Theodore....
No.
레이첼이 칼이랑 나갔대
Rachel's having
drinks with him tonight.
말도 안돼
너한테는 관심도 없으면서
어떻게 그럴 수 있지?
How can she, when she's never
shown interest in you?
잊어버려!
-Forget about her.
-He's right.
그래, 다 잊어버리고 중국에 가
중국 음식이나 먹으라구
Please move on. Go to China.
Eat Chinese food.
거기선 그냥 '음식'이라고
하겠지만
Of course, there
they just call it "food."
그래야겠지, 모르겠어
Yeah, I guess. I don't know.
이거나 대신 전해줄래?
All right, just give her this
for me, okay?
- 걱정 마, 우리가 있잖아
- 알아
We're looking out for you.
We want you to be happy.
우린 네 행복을 바래
맥주 두 병째라 하는 말이지만
널 사랑해, 임마
I may only have a couple beers
in me, but I love you.
난 아직 한 병째야, 난...
I'm still on my first.
넌 참 좋은 친구야
I just think you're nice.
그렇게해서 저하고 친구들이
과일 바구니 사업을 시작했어요
That's when we started
this fruit basket business.
우린 '바구니 삼총사'라고
부른답니다
We call ourselves
"The Three Basketeers."
'삼총사'를 빗대서 말한 거야
Like "The Three Musketeers,"
only with fruit.
오우!
좋아
누구 햄버거 먹을 사람?
-How do you want your burgers?
-Presents first!
안돼, 선물부터 풀고
나중에 먹자
레이첼이 얘기해서가 아니라
선물부터 풀고 보자
We're doing presents first.
잠깐 이리 와봐
Hey, hold on there, tiger.
How are you holding up?
어떻게, 잘 돼가고 있어?
감이 안 좋아
Well, not so good.
She thinks tonight we're gonna...
오늘은 우리 관계를 완성시킬
거라고 생각하는 눈치야
...complete the transaction,
if you know what And you do.
무슨 말인지 알지?
멜라니를 위해 전적으로
희생하는 게 어때?
Have you ever thought about
being there for her?
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
전적으로 희생하라구
You know, just be there for her.
무슨 말이야?
Not following you.
생각해봐
Think about it.
좋아, 이건...
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
누가 준 걸까요?
고마워요, 멜라니
-Thank you, Melanie.
-This one right here is from me.
이건 내 거야
좋아
가볍고 소리가 나네
Okay. It's light. It rattles.
It's...
- '그림 맞추기'잖아
- 신경썼구나
...Travel Scrabble!
고마워
Thank you.
이건 조이 거지?
책인가 보네, 책인 것 같아
This one's from Joey.
It feels like a book, I think it's
a book. And it's a book!
진짜 책이네
'수스 박사'다
It's Dr. Seuss!
그 책을 읽고 힘든 시기를
견뎌냈어
That book got me through
some tough times.
이이 마음 속엔 어린아이가
살고 있어요
There's a little child
inside this man.
의사 얘기가 그걸 없애면
죽을 거래요
The doctors say if they remove it,
he'll die.
- 이건 누구 거야?
- 로스 거야
-Who's this from?
-From Ross.
세상에...
Oh, my God! He remembered!
기억하고 있었네
뭘?
-Remembered what?
-lt was months ago.
몇 달 전에 골동품 가게를
지나가다
We walked by this antique store.
I saw this pin.
창문으로 이 브로치를 봤는데
할머니 거랑 비슷하다고 했거든
I told him it was like one
my grandma had when I was little.
이걸 기억하고 있다니
I can't believe he remembered!
누가 나랑 그림 맞추기
할 사람?
Well, sure, but can you
play it on a plane?
- 예쁘지 않니?
- 정말 예쁘다
It's so pretty!
This must've cost him a fortune.
비싸게 주고 샀겠다
오빠가 이런 면이 있었네
I can't believe it.
캐롤이랑 사랑에 빠졌을 땐
크리스탈 오리도 사줬던 애야
Remember when he
fell in love with Carol...
...and bought her that
expensive crystal duck?
뭐라고?
What did you just say?
크리스탈 오리
Crystal duck.
아니, 아니,
사랑 어쩌고 한 부분...
No, no, no. The "love" part?
맙소사
-Oh, my God!
-Oh, no, no, no.
안돼, 안돼, 안돼
그래, 계속 문질러라
그럼 과거로 돌아갈 테니까
That's good. Just keep rubbing
your head. That'll turn back time.
믿을 수가 없어
믿어지지가 않아
This is unbelievable.
I mean, this is unbelievable!
그래, 이건 정말 큰 사건이야
I know.
This is really, really huge.
아니, 작고 사소하고
보잘 것 없고 무의미한 일이야
No, it's not. It's small.
It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
I don't think any of our lives
will ever be the same ever again.
이젠 우리 사이도 예전 같지
못할 거야, 절대로
말 못하게 하는 리모콘
같은 거 없어?
Is there a mute button on this woman?
난 잘 어울릴 것 같은데
너랑 로스 오빠!
I think this is so great.
I mean, you and Ross!
- 전혀 몰랐어?
- 그래, 몰랐어
-Did you have any idea?
-No, none!
여기 온 첫날 데이트 신청
어쩌고 하는 얘길 했지만
My first night in the city,
he mentioned asking me out...
그 후로 아무 일도 없었어
... but nothing ever happened.
그거 말고 또 뭐라고 해?
나랑 데이트하고 싶어했어?
What else did he say?
Does he wanna go out?
어찌나 절실하게 너한테
빠졌는지
Given that he's in love with you...
커피 한 잔만 하자고 해도
입이 귀까지 찢어졌을걸
... he wouldn't mind getting
a cup of coffee.
로스가 날 좋아했다고?
Ross? All this time?
I've gotta talk to him.
얘길 해봐야겠어
- 지금 중국에 있어
- 진짜 중국
-He's in China!
-The country.
비행기가 안 떠났으면?
Is his flight gone?
무슨 소리야
벌써 이런 거 구경하고 있을걸
Yes! He's watching a woman do this:
갔다구
He's gone!
아니, 45분 후에나
비행기가 출발한다고 써있어
His flight doesn't leave
for 45 minutes.
시간차는 어쩌고?
-What about time difference?
-From here to the airport?
- 여기랑 공항?
- 그래
- 시간 안에 못 갈 거야
- 그래도 가볼래
-You'll never make it!
-I've gotta try.
레이첼, 뭐라고 할 건데?
What'll you say to him?
모르겠어
-I don't know.
-Then you shouldn't go.
그럼 가지 마
그래, 마음만 아프게 할 거라면
서두를 거 없잖아
Right. If you're gonna
break his heart, that can wait.
좋은 소식이면 지금
전하는 게 낫지
But if it's good, tell him now.
모르겠어
일단 얼굴을 봐야지
-Maybe I'll know when I see him.
-All right, does this help?
이걸 봐
이게 도움이 되지 않을까?
아니
No. Look, all I know is, I cannot
wait a week. This is just too big.
일주일이나 기다릴 순 없어
이건 보통 일이 아냐
지금 당장 만나야겠어
갈게, 나중에 보자
I've just gotta talk to him.
Okay, I'll see you later.
레이첼, 나도 너 사랑해
Rachel, I love you!
Deal with me first!
나부터 해결해 줘
됐습니다
All right.
로스!
로스
-Ross! Excuse me, pardon me.
-Your boarding pass?
죄송합니다
- 안녕하세요
- 탑승권을 보여주시겠어요?
- 친구한테 할 얘기가 있어요
I need to talk to my friend.
죄송합니다만 탑승권이 없으면
들어가실 수 없습니다
Sorry, you're not allowed here
without a pass.
알아요, 저기 파란 자켓 입은
사람이 제 친구예요, 잠깐만...
He's right there,
in the blue jacket! Can l?
죄송하지만 규정상
안됩니다
I'm sorry. Federal regulations!
좋아요, 그럼 친구한테
좀 전해줄래요?
Then could you please
just give him a message for me?
굉장히 중요한 일이에요
-This is very important.
-All right. What's the message?
좋아요,
뭐라고 전할까요?
모르겠어요
I don't know.
실례합니다, 선생님
누가 말씀 전해달라고 해서요
Excuse me, sir! Excuse me, sir?
I have a message for you.
뭔데요?
레이첼이란 분이 선물 고맙다고
돌아와서 만나잡니다
Rachel loved the present.
She'll see you when you get back.
뭐요?
What?
토비, 아냐...
무슨 소린지 알 수가 없군
Toby, I don't know
what she's talking about.
레이첼이란 사람 난 몰라
그런 눈으로 보지 마
There's no Rachel.
Don't give me that deep freeze.
조이, 조이, 조이...
Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey!
나 아주 기절하는 줄 알았어
I think I blacked out there
for a minute.
아무 것도 아닌데
It was nothing.
이제 자기 즐겁게 해줄게
Well, now we gotta
find something fun for you.
You know what?
있잖아
난 됐어
자기 한번 더 하자
Forget about me.
Let's give you another turn.
또?
-Me, again?
-Sure. Why not?
그럼, 좋지
누군지 몰라도 내일 근사한
과일 바구니 받겠네
Boy, somebody's gonna get
a big fruit basket tomorrow!
솔직히 있잖아...
자기는 내 생각이랑 딴판이야
I gotta tell you, you are nothing like
I thought you'd be.
무슨 뜻이야?
How do you mean?
자긴 항상 '나, 나, 나'밖에
모르는 사람일 줄 알았거든
I had you pegged as a guy
who's always, "Me, me, me!"
근데 그 반대야
But you, you're a giver.
자기는 세상에서 제일
너그러운 사람이야
You're the most generous man
I ever met.
자긴 꼭 여자 같아
I mean, you're practically a woman.
그렇지?
-You're just saying that.
-No.
A woman!
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 못 만났어
-So?
-I missed him.
- 안됐다
- 저런
-I'm so sorry.
-That's too bad.
정말 안됐다
아무렴
Yeah, right.
진심으로 유감이라고
생각하고 있어
No, I feel bad for her. I do.
만났으면 좋을 텐데
I can think of somebody
other than myself.
난 그만 가서 잘게
All right, I'm going to bed.
생일 축하해, 레이첼
너무 신경쓰지 마
-Happy birthday. Hang in there.
-Thanks.
고마워
신난다!
Yes!
피자 쿠폰이 와서...
Pizza coupons.
좋아, 이거 치우는 거나
도와야지
Okay. You guys want help
cleaning up this mess?
그래
That'd be great.
레이첼, 이 포장지 쓸래?
조금 찢어지긴 했는데...
So, Rach, you wanna save
this wrapping paper?
Are you gonna go for it with Ross
or should I throw it out?
오빠하고는 잘해볼 거야
아님 그냥 넘어갈 거야?
모르겠어
I don't know. I don't know.
공항에 가면서, 집에 오면서
계속 생각했는데
Thought about it
all the way there...
...and I thought about it all the way
back. You know, it's Ross!
다른 사람이 아닌 로스잖아
무슨 말인지 알지? 로스라구
You know what I mean? It's Ross.
그럼!
-Sure!
-Sure.
모르겠어
그냥 직감이 그런데...
I don't know. This is just
my initial gut feeling...
내 생각엔...
... but I'm thinking
it'd be really great.
- 내 생각엔 잘 될 것 같아
- 내 생각도 그래
Oh, my God, me too!
We'd be like friends-in-law!
우린 사돈이 되는 거야
무엇보다 좋은 건 네가 오빠에
대해 전부 알고 있다는 거야
The best part is you already
know all about him.
열 다섯 번째 데이트하는
기분이 들 거야
You start on the 1 5th date.
그래, 열 다섯 번째 데이트하는
기분이 들겠지
But it would be like
starting on the 1 5th date.
내 말이 그 말이야
Another good point.
I mean, on the 1 5th date,
you're already in a very...
열 다섯 번째 데이트하는 거면
가벼운 사이가 아니란 뜻이야
... "relationship-y" place.
You're committed.
서로에게 얽매이게 되지
잘 안 되면 어떡할 거야?
What happens if it doesn't work out?
왜 잘 안 되는데?
-Why isn't it working out?
-Sometimes it doesn't.
글쎄, 그런 경우가 있잖아
- 오빠 용모가 딸리니?
- 뭐?
Is he not cute enough?
Does he not make enough money?
- 돈을 못 벌어?
- 아니, 그냥...
다른 남자가 있나 보지
-No, I'm just
-Maybe there's someone else.
정말이야?
다른 남자가 있는 거야?
-ls there someone else?
-No, there is no one else.
아니, 아무도 없어
근데 왜 우리 오빠를
차버리려는 거야?
Then why are you dumping my brother?
뭐?
- 이봐, 헤픈...
- 쉬!
Hey, big Spender!
헤픈 친구!
아직 자고 있어
She's still asleep.
- 어떻게 됐어?
- 굉장했어
-So how'd it go?
-You know how you think you're great?
너도 항상 침대에서
끝내준다고 생각했지?
그런 걸 물어보는 거 보니까
넌 날 너무 모르는구나
The fact you'd even ask
shows how little you know me.
어젯밤엔 내 스스로 대견해하던
일을 할 수가 없었어
Last night I couldn't do the thing
that usually makes me great.
그래서 다른 방법으로 해봤는데
어떻게 됐게?
So I had to do all this other stuff.
And the response I got! Man, oh, man!
와우! 퍼레이드라도 벌이는 것
같았다니까
It was like a ticker-tape parade!
알아, 퍼레이드 할 때 내 방이
그 길 옆에 있었거든
I know. My room's very, very close
to the parade route.
정말 굉장했어, 멜라니만
그런 게 아니라 나도 좋았어!
It was amazing, and not just for her.
For me too!
갑자기 눈이 안 보이면서
다른 감각이 발달된 기분이랄까
It's like, all of a sudden
I'm blind...
... but all my other senses
are heightened.
한 단계 위로 올라설 수
있을 것 같은 기분이 들었어
It's like I was able
to appreciate it...
...on another level.
너한테 높은 단계가
있는 줄 몰랐는데
-I didn't know you had another level.
-I know. Neither did l!
알아, 나도 그랬다니까
그럼 이제 외국어도 알겠네?
Is something going on with O.J.?
- 스커트 예쁘다, 생일선물?
- 응
Hey, great skirt. Birthday present?
- 누가 준 건데?
- 네가 산 블라우스랑 바꿨어
-From who?
-You.
I exchanged the blouse you got me.
잘했다
Well, it's the thought.
오빠가 탄 비행기가
곧 도착하지 않던가?
Doesn't Ross'flight get in
in a couple hours? At gate 27B?
27B 게이트에?
알아
Yeah. Monica, you know, I've been
thinking about it.
모니카, 생각해봤는데
이렇게 결론을 내렸어
I've decided this Ross thing
is not a good idea.
로스하고의 일은
좋은 생각이 아닌 것 같아
왜?
그런 기분이 들어
로스랑 사귀게 되면...
Why?
I feel like I wouldn't
just be going out with him.
너희 모두랑 사귀는 것
같을 거야
I'd be going out with all of you.
There'd be pressure
- 너무 부담스러워서...
- 무슨 소리, 부담 갖지마
No pressure, no pressure!
아직 아무 사이도 아닌데
넌 벌써...
Nothing has happened,
and you're already so
아냐
I'm not "so." Okay, I was a teensy
bit weird at first...
처음엔 좀 이상하게 굴었지만
안 그럴게, 약속해
... but I'll be good. I promise.
누구세요?
- 칼이야
- 올라와요
-Who is it?
-It's me, Carl.
오빠 몰래 남자를 만나?
-Come on up.
-Behind my brother's back?
이런 소리는 절대
안 할 거니까 걱정하지 마
Is the kind of crazy thing
you won't be hearing from me.
7백 달러 벌었어
-Seven hundred bucks!
-All right, you did it!
정말 해냈구나
과일 먹을래?
Do we have any fruit?
지옥 같은 2주였어
Man, hell of a two weeks.
그래도 뭔가를 배운 것 같은
기분이야
You know what?
I feel I learned something.
그래서, 계속 여자한테
봉사만 할 거야?
You'll stick with this
"all for her" thing?
미쳤냐?
What are you, crazy?
앞 못 보던 사람이 시력을
찾았는데 미쳤다고 더듬거려?
When a blind man gets his sight back,
does he walk around like this?
내가 말했지
차에 에드 베글리 주니어 사진
붙어있는 게 한번만 더 보이면
If I see one more picture
of Ed Begley Jr...
...in that stupid electric car,
I'm gonna shoot myself!
자살해버릴 거라고
오해하지는 마
환경 보호를 반대하는 게 아니라
I'm not against
environmental issues, per se...
그 사람이 맘에 안 들어
...it's just that guy!
나보다 이 남자를 만나는 게
더 좋단 말이지?
I can't believe you'd rather
go out with him than me.
이러지 마
나 지금 데이트 중이잖아
Excuse me, I'm trying
to have a date here.
좋아, 그럼 내 생각 그만해
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
그렇게 안 되지?
Can't do it, can you?
그래, 네 생각하는 게
어떻다고?
I'm thinking about you. So what?
이해가 안 가
이 남자를 왜 만나는 거야?
I don't get it.
What do you see in this guy?
괜찮은 사람 같아
Happens to be a very nice guy.
그게 뭐야
그것도 차라고 끌고 다녀?
I mean, come on, buddy!
Get a real car!
레이첼,
한번만 기회를 줘
Rachel, come on. Give us a chance.
- 그게 쉽지가 않아
- 아니
Ross, it's too hard.
친구들이 이상하게 볼까봐?
무슨 상관이야, 우리가 중요하지
Why, because it'll get weird
for everyone else? This is about us.
난 중학교 때부터
널 사랑했어
I've been in love with you
since the ninth grade.
- 로스, 넌 좋은 친구야
- 알아
You're like my best friend.
If we broke up, and I lost you
- 너랑 헤어지면 널 잃게 돼
- 아니, 아니
왜 헤어질 생각을
하는 거야?
What makes you think that?
사람 사귀었다가
헤어진 적 없어?
Have you been involved
where you haven't broken up?
있지
No.
하지만 그건 한번으로 족해
But it only has to happen once.
우린 서로에게 완벽한
짝이라는 걸 알고 있잖아
You and I both know we are perfect
for each other. Right?
문제는 하나야
너도 나한테 매력을 느끼니?
So the only question is:
Are you attracted to me?
모르겠어
I don't know.
널 그런 쪽으로
바라본 적이 없어서
I mean, I've never looked at you
that way before.
그럼 지금부터 시작해봐
Well, start looking.
- 와우
- 그래!
-Wow.
-Exactly!
차에 사람을 매달고 달리는
심정도 이해가 간다니까
And I'm gonna be the guy...
...caught behind this hammerhead
in traffic!
- 그래요
- 그래
Right! You're right.
- 맞아요
- 그래
- 있잖아요
- 뭐가?
You know what?
깜빡하고 있었는데
공항에 친구 마중나가야 돼요
I'm supposed to pick up
a friend at the airport.
정말 미안해요
I am so sorry!
여기서 마저 술을 마시고
싶으면 그렇게 해요
If you wanna finish your drinks,
please do.
미안하지만 난 가야겠어요
미안해요
-I'm sorry, I gotta go. I'm sorry.
-But....
하지만...
어디 가?
로스 만나러
-Where are you going?
-To get Ross.
정말? 너무 신난다
-My God, this is so exciting!
-I know.
모니카, 있지...
나 오늘 데이트 다 못 끝내니까
알아서 좀 해줘
If you want the rest of my date,
I'm not gonna finish it.
레이첼,
나더러 어떡하라고?
-Rachel, he's not a sandwich.
-No, he's a banker with opera tickets.
오페라 티켓 갖고 있을 거야
Hello!
레이첼, 어디 가?
공항
-Where you going?
-Airport.
안돼, 로스한테 말하지 마
나 아직 할 일이 많단 말야
You can't tell him.
There's so much I haven't done.
'SOS 해상기동대'도
봐야 되고
I haven't watched Baywatch
with Yasmine Bleeth!
챈들러, 걱정하지 마
좋은 일로 가는 거야
Chandler, relax. This is a good
going to the airport.
그래?
그럼 빨리 바람처럼 날아가
Oh, well then fly, good woman,
fly like the wind.
날아간다
내가 바람 밀어준 거
잊지 말고
-I'm flying!
-Tell him I'm the one who blew it!
사랑의 해결사가
또 한 건 해결했군
Yes, another successful case
for the love doctor.
실례합니다, 실례해요
실례합니다
Excuse me! Pardon me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
그만 좀 하라니까
레이첼이란 여자 정말 몰라
Toby, for God's sake,
will you let it go?
There's no Rachel!
실례합니다
이거 떨어졌어
Hey! I got that.
- 고마워, 자기야
- 아냐
-Thanks, sweetie.
-No problem.
빨리 친구들한테
소개시켜주고 싶어
I can't wait for you
to meet my friends.
- 정말?
- 그래
- 날 헐뜯고 놀리지 않을까?
- 아닐 거야
You don't think they'll judge me?
- 빨리 소개해주고 싶어
- 알았어
-No, they will. I just....
-Can't wait!
다들 자기를 좋아할 거야
Come on, they're gonna love you.